Dan Holzman: Please throw out the beanbag chairs. Here we go.
دان هولزمان : من فضلكم إرموا لنا الكراسي الاسفنجية
Barry Friedman: There are all kinds of high-tech chairs here today,
باري فريدمان : هذه هي الكراسي الاكثر تطورا اليوم
but this is really, I think, when it reached its peak
وهي كذلك بالفعل عندما يتعلق الامر
as far as ergonomics, comfort, design, flexibility ...
بالراحة والتصميم والمرونة وامكانية وضعها في اي مكان
DH: Now obviously, this is not something we do on our regular show;
دان هولزمان : وكما يبدو هذا ليس شيئاً نقوم به عادة في عروضنا
it's something we just kind of learned for this,
وهو شيء تدربنا عليه من اجل هذا المؤتمر فحسب
so we're going to try. But can we have some inspirational music for the beanbag chairs?
لذا سوف نجرب ان نتلاعب بهذه الكراسي الاسفنجية .. ولكن هلا شغلتم القليل من الموسيقى التحميسية
BF: Nice show, Daniel, nice show. You are the man!
باري فريدمان : عرض جيد دانيل .. عرض جيد ... انت رائع
Nice show. Man, that was good!
انت رائع .. كان هذا جيدا
DH: Thank you.
دان هولزمان : شكراً
BF: You know, sometimes when people do those, they go all the way down.
باري فريدمان : أتعلم عندما يمارس الناس تمرين الضغط يهبوطون الى الاسفل ... احيانا فحسب
You actually just did that. (Laughter)
بينما انت تقوم بهكذا فحسب
That's the kind of extra effort that's gotten us where we are today ...
يبدو هذا هو نوع المجهود الذي وصل بنا الى ما وصلنا اليه اليوم
DH: All right, let's show them something special.
دان هولزمان : حسنا لنقوم بشيء مميز الآن
BF: ... without a MacArthur grant.
باري فريدمان : شيء لا يتعلق بالمنحة التي حصلنا عليها ؟؟
Yeah, look at this. You know, all kinds of different ...
حسنا .. انظروا الى هذه .. تبدو مميزة
TED is about invention, let's be honest. Right? DH: Yeah, it is.
اتعلمون .. مؤتمر تيد هو في الاساس عن الابداع .. ولنكن صريحين :: دان هولزمان : نعم انه عن الابداع
BF: Last night, Michael Moschen showed some juggling props
باري فريدمان : البارح قام ميشيل موسشين .. بالتلاعب ببعض الدعائم
he has invented and working on.
التي اخترعها وعمل عليها
Right now, Dan's going to show something he actually invented.
والان سوف يريكم دانيل شيئا قد اخترعه هو
DH: A type of juggling I actually invented,
دان هولزمان : نوعا من التلاعب بالاشياء من اختراعه
right after I saw another juggler do it.
بعد ان شاهد لاعب خفة يقوم بها من قبل
BF: Shut up. (Laughter)
باري فريدمان : إصمت
DH: And this is a small excerpt from a longer piece.
دان هولزمان : هذه عينة صغيرة .. اخذت من عينة اكبر
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Folks, this is shaker cup juggling. It's not a showstopper
دان هولزمان : يا رفاق هذا هو عرض التلاعب .. بكؤوس خلط العصائر . .انه ليس العرض الختامي
but it certainly slows it down.
ولكنه حتما يستهلك قليلا من الوقت الذي لدينا
BF: Oh yeah, it does. (Drum roll)
باري فريدمان : نعم انه يستهلك بالفعل
BF: Oh, Daniel.
باري فريدمان : نعم يا دانيل
(Applause)
(تصفيق )
DH: One more? (Drum roll)
دان هولزمان : مرة اخرى
Perfect. (Drum roll)
ممتاز
BF: OK. DH: Oh! All right.
باري فريدمان : حسناً .. آووه :::: دان هولزمان : حسنا
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
I'm now pushing my luck: I'm skipping right to six cups.
والآن سأعتمد على الحظ .. سوف اتلاعب بستة كؤوس
In order to do six cups, I must have perfect control
ولكي اتلاعب بالستة . يجب ان اتحكم بها جيدا
over three with my right hand. (Drum roll)
3 بيدي اليمنى
BF: Also three with his left.
باري فريدمان : و3 باليد اليسرى
DH: Perfect.
دان هولزمان : ممتاز
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
And now, all six cups. Should I do it on the first try
والآنا لستة كؤوس معا .. يجب ان احاول مرة أولى
or should I miss once on purpose? (Laughter)
ام يجب علي القيام بالامر مباشرة
BF: First try? Once on purpose?
باري فريدمان : تجربة أولى .. لا تحسب .. ام محاولة مباشرة
(Audience: Once on purpose!)
الجمهور : مباشرة .. لا تجرب
DH: How about if I try first and then decide?
دان هولزمان : ما رايكم ان اجرب اول مرة .. ومن ثم اقرر ؟
BF: Good idea. (Laughter) Let's leave that. We'll leave that door open.
باري فريدمان : فكرة جيدة . .لنتركه على راحته .. لنتركة على راحته
(Laughter) (Applause)
(ضحك)
DH: He's looking at me.
دان هولزمان : انه ينظر إلي
BF: That's all right, he does that. All right.
باري فريدمان : حسناً . .رائع لقد قام بها ..
DH: Oh! It's time for Richard's help. (Laughter)
دان هولزمان : يجب ان يساعدنا ريتشارد الآن
Oh, good. All right.
آه .. حسناً
BF: You know, over the years, every year at the conference,
باري فريدمان : في كل مرة نأتي بها الى هذا المؤتمر
it's kind of become a tradition for us to do something dangerous
نقوم بأمر خطير وقد غدا هذا عادة لدينا
with Richard. And we've always done something with the bullwhips
طبعا مع ريتشارد .. ودائما نقوم بشيء متعلق بسوط الثيران
in our act. It's funny, for years I did it with Daniel holding balloons.
انه امرٌ ممتع .. وقد كان ذلك لعدة سنوات .. وكنت اقوم بذلك مع دانيل وهو يحمل البالونات
And then we thought, "How stupid."
ولكن قلنا لانفسنا " انه امرٌ غبي "
DH: Excuse me, could we work on the design of the microphone?
دان هولزمان : من فضلكم .. هلا عمل فريق الصوت عمله بصورة صحيحة !
BF: I think that's the next session.
باري فريدمان : اعتقد ان هذا التصليح سيتم في التحدث المقبل
DH: Next session?
دان هولزمان : الجلسة القادمة ؟
BF: Yeah. And so we've actually found a way to incorporate Richard in this.
باري فريدمان : أخيراً وجدنا سبب لكي نعاقب ريتشارد عليه
He actually assumes more of the danger in this.
هو في الاساس يتوقع حدوث امور خطيرة اليوم
DH: Please stand up, Richard. (Whip cracks)
دان هولزمان : من فضلك قم . .ريتشارد
Oh, sorry. (Laughter)
(ضحك)
DH: Now Richard, please ... (Whip cracks)
دان هولزمان : الآن ريتشارد .. من فضلك
BF: OK, sorry.
باري فريدمان : حسناً .. عذراً
DH: Jesus Christ. Richard, please stand in front of me.
دان هولزمان : ياإلهي .. ريتشارد .. قف امامي من فضلك
Richard Wurman: Can I say something?
ريتشارد ورمان : هل يمكنني ان اقول شيئاً
BF: Sure.
دان هولزمان : حتماً
RW: In all past years I've rehearsed with them,
ريتشارد ورمان : في الماضي تدربت معهم
the things that have happened to me --
وكنت اعلم تماما مالذي يخططون له
I have no idea what's going to happen and that's the truth.
ولكن اليوم .. لا فكرة لدي . .وهذه حقيقة
DH: All right, please stand here in front ...
دان هولزمان : من فضلك قف امامي .. احمني
God, I hate that. Put your hands out like this, please.
يا إلهي .. انا اكره هذا ... ضع يديك هكذا من فضلك
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
BF: No, come stay up with him.
باري فريدمان : هيا قف بقربه .. هذا
Dan used to actually hold them but now he's got you for protection.
في الواقع كان دان يحمل البالونات .. ولكنه اليوم يستخدمك كجدار حامي
It's kind of neat. OK.
اعتقد انه امر معيب
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
DH: Wow, you've been working out.
دان هولزمان : ممم .. هل كنت تتدرب
BF: No, shut up!
باري فريدمان : ... إصمت
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
Having a little bit of Richard time. That's nice, that's good.
هذا هو وقت ريتشارد اليوم .. هذا امرٌ جيد
OK, here we go.
حسنا .. لنبدأ
Have him hold your wrist so I can ...
اجعله يمسك ساعدك لكي استطيع ..
DH: Please hold my wrist, will you. BF: Yeah, hold this a minute.
دان هولزمان : امسك ساعدي من فضلك .. دقيقة فحسب
There you go.
باري فريدمان : سنبدأ
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
OK.
حسنا
OK, hold on.
حسنا . اثبت
RW: Hmmm.
باري فريدمان : همممم
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
DH: First one.
دان هولزمان : الأولى
BF: All those mid-year phone calls are coming back to me now, Richard.
باري فريدمان : كل تلك الاتصالات التي جرت بيننا .. بدات تعود الى ذاكرتي الان يا ريتشارد
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
DH: So Richard, what were we on the list? Like 1,020?
دان هولزمان : حسنا ريتشارد اخبرني اين كنا نحن على قائمة المدعوين ؟ رقم 1020
What happened there?
مالذي حدث حينها
BF: I think we were just outside.
باري فريدمان : اعتقد انهم كانوا لن يدعونا اليوم
DH: I don't get it. (Applause)
(تصفيق )
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
DH: Sorry. BF: Having some bad flashbacks.
هناك بعض الاضواء مسلطة علي
RW: Do you want me to hold you or not? DH: Don't hold me that hard.
دان هولزمان : لاتمسكني بهذه القوة
BF: Here we go, I'm taking it. (Balloon pops) (Applause)
باري فريدمان : حسناً .. سأضربها
DH: One more, one more.
دان هولزمان : واحدة اخرى .. واحدة اخرى
BF: We've got one more we're going to do.
باري فريدمان : نريد ان نضرب بالونة اخرى
RW: Do I get to hold them?
ريتشارد : هل سأحملها انا
BF: You don't want to hold these, trust me.
باري فريدمان : صدقني لا تريد حمل هذه
DH: Could you spread your legs a little bit?
دان هولزمان : هلا باعدت قليلا بين رجليك
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
BF: Gloria, you want to do it? It's very cool.
باري فريدمان : غلوريا هل تريدين القيام بذلك ؟ انه امرٌ ممتع
(Applause)
( تصفيق )
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
One more try. Man, I don't want to get too close.
محاولة اخرى .. لا اريد ان اقترب اكثر
Could you just push that?
هلا ابعدت معدتك قليلا الى الخلف ؟
(Applause)
(ضحك)
DH: Wow! Boy!
دان هولزمان : يا سلام !
BF: That's cool. I always wanted to try that.
باري فريدمان : هذا امرٌ ممتع ... لطالما اردت القيام بذلك
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
DH: Let's jump this way, though.
دان هولزمان : دعني اذهب الى هناك
Now, we risked Richard's life, it's only fair we risk our own lives.
الان لقد خاطرنا بحياة ريتشارد .. واعتقد انه من الملائم ان نخاطر بحياتنا ايضا
So to do that, I will juggle these three razor-sharp sickles.
وللقيام بذلك سوف اقوم بالتلاعب بهذه المناجل الحادة
And if that wasn't enough, and judging by your response, it's not ...
وان لم يكن هذا كافيا بالنسبة لكم ... ويبدو ليس كافيا من وجوهكم
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
DH: Wow! BF: Hoping for a little more build.
باري فريدمان : واو ! يريدون اثارة اكثر
DH: True. Barry ...
دان هولزمان : حسنا . .باري
BF: I'm going to run up behind him.
باري فريدمان : سوف اقوم بالقفز من فوقه
DH: Leap over my shoulder.
دان هولزمان : من فوق كتفي
BF: Up and over his shoulders.
باري فريدمان : نعم من فوق كتفه
DH: Grab the blades in mid-air, land right there in a pool of blood ...
دان هولزمان : ومن ثم سامسك المناجل .. وهي في الهواء ... لكي يهبط في بركة من الدماء لاحقا
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
Still juggling. (Laughter)
وهو يتلاعب بهم
Impossible, you say?
مستحيل .. اهكذا تقولون
BF: Incredible, you say?
باري فريدمان : مدهش أهكذا تقولون
DH: Why bother, you say?
دان هولزمان : لماذا هذا العناء أهكذا تقولون
BF: Here we go.
باري فريدمان : حسنا لنبدأ
DH: Just do it juggler boys, you say?
دان هولزمان : هلا قمتم بهذا أهكذا تقولون
BF: This guy, this guy invented air.
باري فريدمان : هذا الرجل .. اكتشف الهواء
DH: I think so, that's right.
دان هولزمان : هكذا اظن . . اليس كذلك
Even the pencil.
وحتى قلم الرصاص
BF: He invented the pencil.
باري فريدمان : لقد اكتشف قلم الرصاص
DH: All right, we'll do this trick, but please remember
دان هولزمان : حسنا.. سنقوم بالتجربة .. ولكن تذكروا
it took us over 10 years to perfect.
لقد تدربنا 10 سنوات لكي نتقنها
BF: Ten years to perfect, which you're about to see.
باري فريدمان : 10 سنوات لاتقان الذي سنقوم به الآن
DH: It's not that difficult, we just don't like to practice that much.
دان هولزمان : الامر ليس بهذه الصعوبة .. الا اننا لا نحب التدرب كثيرا
BF: No, it's a hassle. Traveling too much.
باري فريدمان : هششش .. نحن نسافر كثيرا
Actually, we will take a second to prove --
ربما يجب علينا ان نؤكد لكم ان هذه الخدعة
this could be fake -- that the blades are indeed razor-sharp.
حقيقية .. وان هذه المناجل حادة فعلا
DH: Will someone please throw a small farm animal
دان هولزمان : هلا اعطيتموني حيوانا صغيرا
up onto the stage?
لكي اذبحه هنا على المسرح
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
Or a virgin for a sacrifice?
او عذراء لكي نضحي بها
BF: Anything?
باري فريدمان : اي شيء
DH: Where's Gloria? (Laughter)
دان هولزمان : أين غلوريا
BF: No, she's got ... farm animal.
باري فريدمان : لا .. لديها حيوان أليف
DH: Do you have a small farm animal?
دان هولزمان : هل لديك حيوان أليف ؟
Just trying to play the odds. All right, here we go.
على الاقل حاولت
BF: Over the top, over the top.
باري فريدمان : حسنا من فوقه .. من فوقه
DH: How you feeling, Barry? You feeling all right?
دان هولزمان : كيف تشعر يا باري .. هل تشعر انك بخير
BF: Yeah, it's all right.
باري فريدمان : نعم اشعر اني بخير
DH: Do you feel everything's OK? The atmosphere, the ...
دان هولزمان : هل تشعر ان كل شيء على مايرام ؟ .. الجو المحيط ؟
BF: Yeah, a little sketchy.
باري فريدمان : نعم انه الاجواء متوترة قليلا
DH: Everything up here's OK?
دان هولزمان : هل شيء هنا جيدا ؟
BF: Yeah.
باري فريدمان : نعم
DH: Then here we go.
دان هولزمان : حسنا لنبدأ
BF: This one's a little ... Who's doing the lights? Could you
باري فريدمان : هنالك ضوء يضرب مباشرة .. من المسوؤل عن الانارة . ؟ هلا ارفعت حده قليلا
point that a little more directly
هذا الذي يشير مباشرة إلي
into my eyeballs? Is that possible? (Laughter) I can still see a little.
تماما في منتصف عيني ؟ هل هذا ممكن ، هلا تعميني اكثر .. فما زلت استطيع الرؤية
DH: And turn up the intensity; we're still pink in the middle.
دان هولزمان : إرفع حدة الاضاءة لعلنا نحترق
We went too far. (Laughter)
أعتقد اننا بالغنا قليلا
BF: Yeah, it's too far. It's too much of a visual.
باري فريدمان : نعم اعتقد ذلك .. هنالك الكثير من الاضاءة فحسب
The design of the body is a whole different thing.
كل الامر يتعلق بالجسد .. انه امرٌ مختلف تماما
DH: Ready, Barry? BF: Over the top.
دان هولزمان : جاهز باري ..باري فريدمان : من فوق كتفيك
DH: May we have our jumping music please? (Silence)
دان هولزمان : هلا شغلتم الموسيقى الخاصة بالقفز
May we have it a bit louder?
أعلى قليلا من فضلكم
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
BF: They're a good crew! Whoa!
باري فريدمان : انهم طاقم رائع
DH: Whoa, sorry. All right.
دان هولزمان : حسنا . حسنا
BF: We're going on.
باري فريدمان : هذه للاحماء فحسب
DH: All right, we'll try again.
دان هولزمان : حسنا .. سنحاول مرة أخرى
BF: All right? Oh my gosh. Oh.
باري فريدمان : حسنا .. ياإلهي
DH: All right, here we go. Sorry about that.
دان هولزمان : آسف من اجل هذا
BF: I thought I had the hard part. OK.
باري فريدمان : ظننت انني اقوم بالامر الصعب !
DH: Whenever you're ready.
دان هولزمان : انا جاهز عندما تكون انت جاهز
BF: There we go!
باري فريدمان : ها قد قمنا بها
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
All right, get up! Come on and dance! DH: Dance, come on. BF: Come on and dance!
تعال .. تعال وارقص معي .. تعال
Somebody dance! Come on!
ارقصوا معنا .. هيا
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Wow, wow, OK, stop.
وااو .. واااو .. حسنا قف !
Weird, no one dances. We're two guys doing this. (Laughter)
غريب .. لم يرقص احدٌ من الجمهور ... نحن فحسب
I think that's uncomfortable for everyone.
اعتقد ان هذا غير مريح بالنسبة لهم
DH: The French judge ...
دان هولزمان : انهم كالحكام الفرنسيون
BF: One more quick thing.
باري فريدمان : هادؤون جدا
DH: The French judge gives it a 5.2.
دان هولزمان : والحكام الفرنسيون يعطون علامة 5.2
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
BF: Well, you know ...
باري فريدمان : حسنا كما تعلمون
DH: There you go ... BF: Oh, yeah. Another one coming in.
دان هولزمان : خذ هذه ..باري فريدمان : واحدة اخرى ايضا
DH: Tell them about our bio and stuff.
دان هولزمان : اخبرهم عن سيرتنا الذاتية
BF: Yeah. In our bio, some of you may have read
باري فريدمان : نعم .. في سيرتنا الذاتية التي ربما قرأتم بعضها
that we've won two world juggling championships.
مكتوب اننا ربحنا مسابقتين في الرمي والتلاعب
And believe it or not, you don't win juggling champions
وهل تعلمون ان ربح تلك المسابقات
for doing things with bullwhips or shaker cups.
لايتم بسوط الثيران .. او برمي كؤوس الخلط
We're going to show you right now
والان سوف نريكم العرض الرسمي
an excerpt from a routine that we used
الاعتيادي الذي نقوم به
to wipe out the other juggling team competition.
لكي نتغلب على منافسينا
DH: That's right.
دان هولزمان : نعم هذا صحيح
BF: Good.
باري فريدمان : حسنا
DH: I know what you're thinking: other juggling teams must really suck.
دان هولزمان : أعرف ما تفكرون به الآن .. تقولون .. إن استطاعوا الربح فهذا بسبب ان المنافسين كانوا سيئين حقاً
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
BF: Juggling's got a bad rap.
باري فريدمان : فرمي الاشياء له سمعة سيئة
DH: But wait, Barry, there's still one more club lying there by my foot.
دان هولزمان : انتظر ما زال هناك واحدة هنا بقرب قدمي
And look, it has a twin!
انظر انهما اثنتين
BF: Shut up. (Laughter)
(ضحك)
DH: There's still one more by my foot.
هنالك واحدة بقرب قدمي
What do you want me to do with it?
مالذي تريد مني ان اقوم به حيالها ؟
BF: Richard you tell him, it's your last year. (Laughter)
باري فريدمان : ريتشارد .. ريتشارد اخبرهم انها سنتك الاخيرة
DH: That's a pretty good setup, Richard.
دان هولزمان : انها تحتاج لاعداد كبير .. ريتشارد
BF: Yeah, it's a good setup. That's a big setup.
باري فريدمان : نعم نعم .. اعداد جيد .. اعداد كبير
DH: You can't get any better than that. All right. What I will do: I will use my panther-like reflexes.
دان هولزمان : حسنا مالذي سأقوم به .. سوف استخدم شريكي لتلقي كل هذه لكي اقوم ب ...
BF: Nice.
باري فريدمان : جميل
DH: I got that --
دان هولزمان :
to reach down and grab that club in my grip of steel.
سوف اهبط وامسك بها بعلاقة مفاتيحي !
BF: Nice.
باري فريدمان : جميل
DH: I touched it, Barry. That should be enough.
دان هولزمان : لقد لمستها باري .. لمستها . اعتقد ان هذا كافي
BF: It's progress, that's the thing.
باري فريدمان : انه تقدم جيد .. هذه هي الفكرة
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
DH: How about that? I'll do it again.
دان هولزمان : ما رأيك الآن ؟
Oh wait, it's on your side, Barry.
آه انظر .. انها بقربك الان يا باري ..
And it's awfully windy over there.
يالها من رياح قوية هنا
BF: It is, it's weird. You wouldn't think
باري فريدمان : نعم انه امر غريب اليس كذلك
it would affect half the stage, but it is. It's weird.
لا بد انها اثرت على نصف الحضور .. ياله من امر غريب
Watch this: what I'm going to do is slide the seventh one onto my foot.
انظر الى هذا .. سوف اقوم بزلقها الى قدمي
DH: Wow! What a great trick, Barry!
دان هولزمان : ياه .. خدعة جميلة يا باري
Oh, look how it lies there.
آه .. انظر كيف تستلقي هناك
Oh, Barry, is there nothing you can't do?
آه يا باري .. انت محطم الصعاب كلها
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
You are my hero. You're my Jim Shea, Jr.
انت بطلي الشخصي .. انت جيم شيا الصغير
Too much Olympics.
انت كل اللاعبين الاولمبين
BF: From my foot, I'll attempt to kick the seventh club. Here we go.
باري فريدمان : حسنا ساحاول بقدمي ان التقط هذه اركل هذه السابعة
DH: Where, Barry? Where? Tell us, Barry.
دان هولزمان : الى اين يا باري .. الى اين .. اخبرنا
[Unclear] eagerly awaits your next syllable. What will it be?
انتظر فحسب .. ماذا سيحدث
What gem of knowledge?
يا بحر من العلوم
What pearl of wisdom?
يا بحر من الحكمة
Do you want to buy a vowel, Barry?
هل تريد ان تبيت استخارة باري ؟
Is that your final answer?
هل هذه هي اجابتك النهائية
BF: All right! You have to turn off the TV from time to time.
باري فريدمان : هلا صمت قليلا .. !
DH: I do, I do.
دان هولزمان : حسنا حسنا
BF: From my foot, the kick up in the seven.
ساحاول بقدمي ان ارفع السابعة
DH: We will juggle seven.
دان هولزمان : نعم سنرمي سبعة
BF: From six to seven. DH: That's a world's record. BF: Really? DH: For us.
باري فريدمان : من ستة الى سبعة .. دان هولزمان : انه عدد جديد بالنسبة لنا
BF: Yes.
باري فريدمان : نعم
DH: Whenever you're ready there, big guy.
دان هولزمان : انا مستعد عندما تكون انت كذلك .. ايها الكبير
Put your tongue away, Barry.
ابعد لسانك قليلا ... باري
BF: Oh, oh, whoa.
باري فريدمان : وها ..هي
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
DH: Please, please stay seated. Stay seated. Thank you.
دان هولزمان : من فضلكم لا تقوموا .. من فضلكم .. شكرا
Because now, to make this twice as difficult,
لاننا سنصعب الامر اكثر الان
we'll juggle the seven clubs back ...
لاننا سوف نرمي هذه السبعة الى الوراء
BF: Seven-club juggling.
باري فريدمان : نعم السبعة
DH: ... to back.
دان هولزمان : الى الوراء
BF: Thank you, that's it.
باري فريدمان : هذه .. هي شكراً
BF: Thank you guys!
باري فريدمان : شكرا يا رفاق
DH: Thank you very much!
دان هولزمان : شكرا جزيلا لكم